Guide to the Claudia Kolker Papers
University of Houston Libraries
Claudia Kolker Papers
1955-2014
1989-2014
02/2014-019
Kolker, Claudia
15.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection contains research and draft materials from Claudia’s book and journalist work such as notes, editors’ commentary, final publications, promotional materials, and more. Claudia’s journals written during the drafting of her book are also included.
Biographical Information:
Claudia Kolker is a Mexican-American journalist who has served on editorial boards for the Los Angeles Times, the Houston Chronicle, and more. Her work has been featured in The Washington Post, The Boston Globe, The Economist, O: The Oprah Magazine, Slate, and Salon. She has reported from El Salvador, Mexico, India, and the Caribbean on politics, religion, and more. In 2011, she published her first book, titled The Immigrant Advantage: What We Can Learn from Newcomers to America about Health, Happiness and Hope. She lives in Houston with her two children.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Genre/Form of Material:
Articles; Correspondence; Manuscripts (document genre); Publications (document genre); Research (document genres)
Personal Name:
Kolker, Claudia
Topical Term:
Emigration and immigration; Immigration & society
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains research and draft materials from Claudia’s book and journalist work such as notes, editors’ commentary, final publications, promotional materials, and more. Claudia’s journals written during the drafting of her book are also included.
Detailed List of Contents
- The Immigrant Advantage, id164599
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials related to Claudia Kolker’s book, The Immigrant Advantage: What We Can Learn from Newcomers to America about Health, Happiness, and Hope, including manuscripts, bibliographic material, interview notes, publicity, etc.
  - Drafts and Manuscripts, id164602
    - Introduction Drafts, 2010; id164606 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Vietnamese Money Club Drafts, 2010; id164607 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Vietnamese Money Club Drafts, Continued, 2010; id164608 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Mexican Cuarentena Drafts, 2010; id164609 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Mexican Cuarentena Drafts, Continued, 2010; id164610 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - South Asian Assisted Marriage Drafts, 2010; id164611 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - South Asian Assisted Marriage Drafts, Continued, 2010; id164612 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Koran and Chinese Afterschools Drafts, 2010; id164613 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - West Indian Multigenerational Households Drafts, 2010; id164614 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - West Indian Multigenerational Households Drafts, Continued, 2010; id164615 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Barrio Stoops, Sidewalks, and Shops Drafts, 2010; id164616 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Barrio Stoops, Sidewalks, and Shops Drafts, Continued, 2010; id164617 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Conclusion Drafts, 2010; id164618 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Complete Drafts, Part 1, 2010-2011; id164619 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Complete Drafts, Part 2, 2010-2011; id164620 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Complete Drafts, Part 3, 2010-2011; id164621 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Vietnamese Monthly Rice Drafts, 2010; id164622 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bibliography and Endnote Drafts, 2010-2011; id164623 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Editorial and Peer Review Feedback, Part 1, 2009-2011; id164624 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Editorial and Peer Review Feedback, Part 2, 2009-2011; id164625 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographic Research, id164603
    - Introduction, 1998-2011; id164628 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Introduction, Continued, 1998-2011; id164629 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Money Club, 1995-2011; id164630 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Assisted Marriage, 2006-2011; id164631 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Multigenerational Households, 1995-2011; id164632 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Multigenerational Households, Continued, 1995-2011; id164633 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Barrio Stoops, Sidewalks, and Shops, Part 1, 2006-2011; id164634 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Barrio Stoops, Sidewalks, and Shops, Part 2, 2006-2011; id164635 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Barrio Stoops, Sidewalks, and Shops, Part 3, 2006-2011; id164636 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Afterschool Study Programs, Part 1, 1997-2011; id164637 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Afterschool Study Programs, Part 2, 1997-2011; id164638 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Afterschool Study Programs, Part 3, 1997-2011; id164639 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cuarentena, Part 1, 1983-2011; id164640 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cuarentena, Part 2, 1983-2011; id164641 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cuarentena, Part 3, 1983-2011; id164642 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Conclusion, 1955-2011; id164643 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Notes, id164644
    - Interview Notes, id164646
      - Notebooks, Part 1, 2008-2011; id164651 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Notebooks, Part 2, 2008-2011; id164652 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Interview Transcripts and Notes, Part 1, 2008-2011; id164653 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Interview Transcripts and Notes, Part 2, 2008-2011; id164654 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Interview Transcripts and Notes, Part 3, 2008-2011; id164655 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Feedback From Friends, id164647
      - Draft Feedback from Friends, 2008-2011; id164657 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, id164648
      - General Notes, To-Do Lists, 2008-2011; id164659 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Community Health Leaders, 2011; id164660 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Researcher Bios, 2011; id164661 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 2011; id164662 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Complete Promotional Materials, 2011; id164663 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - "Conversations beyond the Book: What We Can Learn from Newcomers to America About Health, Happiness, and Hope", id164665 (Ovsbox 10, Item 115)
      - "Welcome to the Book Launch Party" poster, id164666 (Ovsbox 10, Item 116)
  - Notecards, id164645
    - Tutoring Notecards, 2011; id164669 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conclusion Notecards, 2011; id164670 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cuarentena Notecards, 2011; id164671 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Multigenerational Notecards, 2011; id164672 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Money Club Notecards, id164673 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Introduction Notecards, id164674 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Little Village Notecards, id164675 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Journalism, id164600
  This series contains materials related to Claudia work as a journalist and staff writer, including drafts, research, notes, and final published articles.
  - Freelance Work, id164676
    - Quinceañera and Comadres, Notes and Correspondence, 2006; id164682 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Quinceañera and Comadres, Article Research, 2006; id164683 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Unattributed Freelance Notes, 2006; id164684 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hurricane Katrina Article Research, 2006; id164685 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Malcolm Gladwell Articles, 2006; id164686 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Mental Health Articles, 2011; id164687 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Arizona Ethnic Studies Article Research, 2010; id164688 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Research, 2006-2011; id164689 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle - Discrimination Lawsuit, 2009; id164690 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Journalism/Freelance, 1985-1990; id164691 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - “Vernon moms not all getting adequate level of prenatal care”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164692 (Ovsbox 8, Item 1)
    - “Petri, local officials oppose wheelchair bus lift rules”, Sheboygan Press, December 1989; id164693 (Ovsbox 8, Item 2)
    - “Silence is golden on floor of House”, North Jersey Herald & News, March 1990; id164694 (Ovsbox 8, Item 3)
    - “Petri promises to shun $296,979 loophole fund”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164695 (Ovsbox 8, Item 4)
    - “Burlington school honored for anti-drug program”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164696 (Ovsbox 8, Item 5)
    - “SBA becomes proving ground for Engeleiter”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164697 (Ovsbox 8, Item 6)
    - “Machine Products’ troubles date back 11 years”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164698 (Ovsbox 8, Item 7)
    - “USDA may slash price supports on milk 50 cents”, The Sheboygan Press, December 1989; id164699 (Ovsbox 8, Item 8)
    - “State activists seek tougher Lakes’ cleanup plan”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164700 (Ovsbox 8, Item 9)
    - “Wisconsin ranked as 8th best-run state”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1990; id164701 (Ovsbox 8, Item 10)
    - “Pirate image boosts Wisconsin’s ranking”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164702 (Ovsbox 8, Item 11)
    - “Group denounces El Salvador policy”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1990; id164703 (Ovsbox 8, Item 12)
    - “Church leaders rap Salvadoran action: Gross human rights abuses alleged”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164704 (Ovsbox 8, Item 13)
    - “Federal action in drug war OK, Hanaway says”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164705 (Ovsbox 8, Item 14)
    - “Kasten is against financing Soviet economic restructuring”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164706 (Ovsbox 8, Item 15)
    - “Sustainable ag roots deepend: Wisconsin leads movement”, Wisconsin State Journal, July 1989; id164707 (Ovsbox 8, Item 16)
    - “Aspin among leaders in travel at taxpayers’ expense”, Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164708 (Ovsbox 8, Item 17)
    - “Thompson takes state’s case to White House”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164709 (Ovsbox 8, Item 18)
    - “Thompson: State may lease Chippewa fishing rights”, Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164710 (Ovsbox 8, Item 19)
    - “Kohl opposes new telephone technology”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164711 (Ovsbox 8, Item 20)
    - “Private bills a dwindling lot”, Sheboygan Press, February 1990; id164712 (Ovsbox 8, Item 21)
    - “State lawmakers divided over attack”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164713 (Ovsbox 8, Item 22)
    - “Study urges 1982-86 amnesty period”, San Antonio Light, November 1988; id164714 (Ovsbox 8, Item 23)
    - “Gunderson, Gingrich share goal: Republican representatives want their party to gain control of the House”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164715 (Ovsbox 8, Item 24)
    - “Gunderson, Sensenbrenner criticized: Planned Middle East trip questioned”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164716 (Ovsbox 8, Item 25)
    - “A head of her time: State native became toast of Washington”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164717 (Ovsbox 8, Item 26)
    - “Racinian out to make noise: Bray wants ‘silent generation’ to help fix country”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164718 (Ovsbox 8, Item 27)
    - “Dairy industry faces technological dilemmas: Biotechnical cattle research will increase milk production and create Texas ‘super herds’”, Houston Chronicle, November 1988; id164719 (Ovsbox 8, Item 28)
    - Page 3A, The Journal times, November 1989; id164720 (Ovsbox 8, Item 29)
    - “Kasten tutors East Bloc on how freedom works”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164721 (Ovsbox 8, Item 30)
    - “Kasten abandons Armenian bill”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164722 (Ovsbox 8, Item 31)
    - “Bill would help Hmong refugees become citizens of United States”, The Sheboygan Press, April 1990; id164723 (Ovsbox 8, Item 32)
    - “Estimates indicate state won’t lose seat”, The Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164724 (Ovsbox 8, Item 33)
    - “Mr. Smith again goes to D.C.”, The Journal Times, April 1989; id164725 (Ovsbox 8, Item 34)
    - “New SBA chief Engeleiter faces overwhelming job”, The Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164726 (Ovsbox 8, Item 35)
    - “Inouye invited to Wisconsin: Senator to witness efforts to resolve treaty issue”, The Sheboygan Press, March 1990; id164727 (Ovsbox 8, Item 36)
    - “Reapportionment may void feeling of relief from census”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164728 (Ovsbox 8, Item 37)
    - “Is Engeleiter’s post a dead-end job?”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164729 (Ovsbox 8, Item 38)
    - “Changing the Constitution: How can it be accomplished?”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164730 (Ovsbox 8, Item 39)
    - Page 3A, The Journal Times, August 1989; id164731 (Ovsbox 8, Item 40)
    - “Wisconsin leader organic farming”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164732 (Ovsbox 8, Item 41)
    - “Lawmakers try 200-year-old way to change Constitution”, Wisconsin State Journal, July 1989; id164733 (Ovsbox 8, Item 42)
    - “Thompson hopeful of wider U.S. role in solving treaty disputes”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164734 (Ovsbox 8, Item 43)
    - “Kastenmeier has new approach for nation’s dairy supply”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164735 (Ovsbox 8, Item 44)
    - “Most quit farming voluntarily: Study”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164736 (Ovsbox 8, Item 45)
    - “Phone-caller ID a privacy issue”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164737 (Ovsbox 8, Item 46)
    - “Looking for a few good kids: State congressmen part of pipeline to the Marines ”, La Crosse Tribune, September 1989; id164738 (Ovsbox 8, Item 47)
    - “Biotechnical research causes controversy among dairy farmers and cattle raisers”, San Antonio Light, November 1988; id164739 (Ovsbox 8, Item 48)
    - “Military gays gain lawmaker’s support”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1990; id164740 (Ovsbox 8, Item 49)
    - “Ag budget starts off better”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164741 (Ovsbox 8, Item 50)
    - “Cotton Council Hammers Out Legislative Goals”, The Commercial Dispatch, February 1989; id164742 (Ovsbox 8, Item 51)
    - “Gunderson into Virginia real estate market”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1990; id164743 (Ovsbox 8, Item 52)
    - “Proxmire defers to wife, is making new home in D.C.”, The Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164744 (Ovsbox 8, Item 53)
    - “Spit and polish: Winning appointment to military academy means you’ve got to shine in interview”, The Sheboygan Press, October 1989; id164745 (Ovsbox 8, Item 54)
    - “Kohl sponsors bill to protect Great Lakes”, La Crosse Tribune, September 1989; id164746 (Ovsbox 8, Item 55)
    - “7 state groups want tougher clean-air laws”, The Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164747 (Ovsbox 8, Item 56)
    - “Gov. Thompson seeks spearing solution in D.C.”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164748 (Ovsbox 8, Item 57)
    - “Wright goes on the defense”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1989; id164749 (Ovsbox 8, Item 58)
    - “Federal help asked for Hmong education”, The Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164750 (Ovsbox 8, Item 59)
    - “Wisconsin man denied Medal of Honor”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164751 (Ovsbox 8, Item 60)
    - “Thompson praises acid rain proposal”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164752 (Ovsbox 8, Item 61)
    - “State’s Congressmen Pocketed $31,000 In Honoraria During Past Five Years”, The Commercial Dispatch, April 1989; id164753 (Ovsbox 8, Item 62)
    - “Defense Contract Booty Surges 63%: 1988 Was A Banner Year”, The Commercial Dispatch, March 1989; id164754 (Ovsbox 8, Item 63)
    - “Ethics Probe Raises ‘Serious Questions’”, The Commercial Dispatch, April 1989; id164755 (Ovsbox 8, Item 64)
    - “Lott, 9 Others Want Exxon To Pay $50M For Cleanup”, The Commercial Dispatch, April 1989; id164756 (Ovsbox 8, Item 65)
    - “State spelling champ survives, competes today”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164757 (Ovsbox 8, Item 66)
    - “Mississippi Lawmakers Give Bush’s Speech ‘Thumbs Up’: Education Focus Given Extra Kudos”, The Commercial Dispatch, February 1989; id164758 (Ovsbox 8, Item 67)
    - “2,000 State Farmers Are Late On Federally Financed Loans”, The Commercial Dispatch, March 1989; id164759 (Ovsbox 8, Item 68)
    - “Kohler High shares spotlight”, The Sheboygan Press, September 1989; id164760 (Ovsbox 8, Item 69)
    - “Gingrich has plans for Rep. Gunderson”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1989; id164761 (Ovsbox 8, Item 70)
    - “Former Braves’ star makes pitch for old-timers”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164762 (Ovsbox 8, Item 71)
    - “Caracas punks”, The Daily Journal, September 1984; id164763 (Ovsbox 8, Item 72)
    - “Ateneo ‘Macbeth’ fiery, innovative”, The Daily Journal, August; id164764 (Ovsbox 8, Item 73)
    - “Judge rejects limit on spearing”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164765 (Ovsbox 8, Item 74)
    - “Kasten is popular figure at Gallaudet”, Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164766 (Ovsbox 8, Item 75)
    - “Inouye to help on spearfishing”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164767 (Ovsbox 8, Item 76)
    - “Sensenbrenner trip had ‘educational value’”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164768 (Ovsbox 8, Item 77)
    - “Scandal Tours Get Inside Capital”, The Trentonian, March 1989; id164769 (Ovsbox 8, Item 78)
    - “Don’t leave home without it: Racine man awarded patent for stick-on condom carrier”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1990; id164770 (Ovsbox 8, Item 79)
    - “For a light lunch, liberals go out for Chinese in D.C.: Wisconsin is main course of conversation”, Wisconsin State Journal, September 1989; id164771 (Ovsbox 8, Item 80)
    - “UW lobbies for military change”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164772 (Ovsbox 8, Item 81)
    - “Kohl joins effort to limit congressional terms”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164773 (Ovsbox 8, Item 82)
    - “Lawmakers who say they oppose honorariums collected nearly $170,000 in appearance fees”, The Sheboygan Press, March 1989; id164774 (Ovsbox 8, Item 83)
    - “Mr. Smith seeing red over colorized films”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164775 (Ovsbox 8, Item 84)
    - “25% heating-aid cut proposal: Officials fear poor could face hunger, illness”, The Sheboygan Press, February 1990; id164776 (Ovsbox 8, Item 85)
    - “Gunderson signs bill to House”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164777 (Ovsbox 8, Item 86)
    - “Collect ‘em or swap ‘em, they’re congressional cards... but without bubblegum”, La Crosse Tribune, October 1989; id164778 (Ovsbox 8, Item 87)
    - “BGH debate boils down to: Can you trust the FDA?”, LA Crosse Tribune, Feburary 1990; id164779 (Ovsbox 8, Item 88)
    - “Further amnesty is urged: Group would extend entry year to 1986”, El Paso Herald Pos, November 1988; id164780 (Ovsbox 8, Item 89)
    - “Cisneros asks Bush to meet Salinas”, The Brownsville Herald, November 1988; id164781 (Ovsbox 8, Item 90)
    - “Rally is a family affair for Sheboygan woman”, The Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164782 (Ovsbox 8, Item 91)
    - “Lawmakers to fight mail-order taxes”, The Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164783 (Ovsbox 8, Item 92)
    - “Earth Day 20 years old”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1989; id164784 (Ovsbox 8, Item 93)
    - “Petri questions plan to help Hmong vets”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1990; id164785 (Ovsbox 8, Item 94)
    - “Bills aim at biotech ‘vaccuum’”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1989; id164786 (Ovsbox 8, Item 95)
    - “McCoy part of military’s tug-of-war”, La Crosse Tribune, October 1989; id164787 (Ovsbox 8, Item 96)
    - “State black women in health-care bind”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164788 (Ovsbox 8, Item 97)
    - “Biotech beefs up cheese”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164789 (Ovsbox 8, Item 98)
    - “Doubts raised about previous BGH research”, The Sheboygan Press, February 1990; id164790 (Ovsbox 8, Item 99)
    - “Congressmen vie on impact of resignation”, LA Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164791 (Ovsbox 8, Item 100)
    - “Constituents Urge Congressmen to Stall 50% Pay Raises: Mississippi Delegation Getting Mail”, The Commercial Dispatch, February 1989; id164792 (Ovsbox 8, Item 101)
    - “Aspirin loses longtime aide”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164793 (Ovsbox 8, Item 102)
    - “7 state groups want tougher clean-air laws”, The Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164794 (Ovsbox 8, Item 103)
    - “Study: Motor Vehicles Are Greatest Threat To Our Children”, The Commercial Dispatch, March 1989; id164795 (Ovsbox 8, Item 104)
    - “Bishops smooth out organizational problems: National conference focuses on relief for Third World countries”, San Antonio Light, November 1988; id164796 (Ovsbox 8, Item 105)
    - “Governor: Trade pacts outdated”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164797 (Ovsbox 8, Item 106)
    - “Obey: State must back negotiations”, Wisconsin State Journal, September 1989; id164798 (Ovsbox 8, Item 107)
    - “Remains of Indians being relinquished”, Sheboygan Press, September 1989; id164799 (Ovsbox 8, Item 108)
    - “Fort McCoy among 5 sites eyed for large Army training center”, Sheboygan Press, October 1989; id164800 (Ovsbox 8, Item 109)
    - “Many congressmen like spearing plan: But Sensenbrenner vows fight”, The Sheboygan Press, October 1989; id164801 (Ovsbox 8, Item 110)
    - Page 3A, The Journal Times, October 1989; id164802 (Ovsbox 8, Item 111)
    - “Petri loses House battle over census”, The Journal Times, October 1989; id164803 (Ovsbox 8, Item 112)
    - “Kohl raps accuracy of deficit”, The Journal Times, October 1989; id164804 (Ovsbox 8, Item 113)
    - “Plan removes Social Security from budget”, Wisconsin State Journal, October 1989; id164805 (Ovsbox 8, Item 114)
    - “Kohl sponsors bill that affects deficit”, La Crosse Tribune, October 1989; id164806 (Ovsbox 8, Item 115)
    - “Company, feds do not agree on probe basis”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164807 (Ovsbox 8, Item 116)
    - “Artists argue for rights”, Wisconsin State Journal, October 1989; id164808 (Ovsbox 8, Item 117)
    - “Petri pledges to vote against proposed wage increase for politicians, officials”, The Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164809 (Ovsbox 8, Item 118)
    - “State delegation divided on flag decision”, The Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164810 (Ovsbox 8, Item 119)
    - “Kasten, Kohl vote to override veto”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164811 (Ovsbox 9, Item 1)
    - “Former Sen. Nelson catches heat at roast”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1990; id164812 (Ovsbox 9, Item 2)
    - “Proxmire calls Washington home”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164813 (Ovsbox 9, Item 3)
    - “Wisconsin legislators view Wright’s leaving differently”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164814 (Ovsbox 9, Item 4)
    - “Petri donated ’88 honorariums to charity, financial report says”, The Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164815 (Ovsbox 9, Item 5)
    - “Kohl proposal would ban all biological weapons”, The Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164816 (Ovsbox 9, Item 6)
    - “Bush blunt on funding education”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164817 (Ovsbox 9, Item 7)
    - “Kasten at briefing on foreign policy”, The Sheboygan Press, December 1989; id164818 (Ovsbox 9, Item 8)
    - “Aspin, Petri hail U.S. Troop reduction plan”, The Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164819 (Ovsbox 9, Item 9)
    - “Treaty negotiations probed: Senate leader gets status report from tribe”, La Crosse Tribune, December 1989; id164820 (Ovsbox 9, Item 10)
    - “Environmental wish list has 3 state sites”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164821 (Ovsbox 9, Item 11)
    - “Wisconsin lawmakers differ on House override action”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164822 (Ovsbox 9, Item 12)
    - “Rural jobs program may pay off for area”, La Crosse Tribune, January 1990; id164823 (Ovsbox 9, Item 13)
    - “Aspin votes for pay raise”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164824 (Ovsbox 9, Item 14)
    - “State objects to acid rain cleanup subsidies”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164825 (Ovsbox 9, Item 15)
    - “County’s homeless funds cut”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164826 (Ovsbox 9, Item 16)
    - “East Germany popular with local travelers”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164827 (Ovsbox 9, Item 17)
    - “Trips to Germany increasing since Wall crumbled”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164828 (Ovsbox 9, Item 18)
    - “Local Congressmen toe party line”, La Crosse Tribune, January 1990; id164829 (Ovsbox 9, Item 19)